Guide to the Lacrosse records, 1937-ongoing UA.13.02.0009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Lacrosse records
1937-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Sports Information Office
UA.13.02.0009
6.3 Linear Feet
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. The collection includes clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, programs and press brochures/media guides about the men and women's lacrosse team at Duke University. The material ranges in date from 1937-ongoing.
6,700 Items
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Lacrosse records were received by the University Archives as a transfer over time.
Historical Note
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. For many years, the SI Office has maintained records, photographs and other material about Duke athletic teams.
Collection Overview
The collection includes clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, programs and press brochures/media guides for the men and women's lacrosse teams at Duke University. The material dates from 1937-ongoing.
Related Material
Athletic Dept. Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Scrapbooks.
University Archives, Duke University.
Photograph Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Photographic Negative Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Chanticleer Photograph Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Athletic Council Records.
University Archives, Duke University.
Athletics Reference Collection.
University Archives, Duke University.
Duke University -- Sports; Duke University -- Lacrosse -- History -- 20th century; Duke University. Sports Information Office; Duke University. Sports Information Office
- Yearly Files, 1937-2001 1937-2001, 7 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  The Yearly files contain clippings, press releases, statistics, rosters, and programs about the lacrosse team at Duke University.
  - Men's Lacrosse, 1937-2000
    - 1937-1973 (Box 1)
    - 1974-1988 (Box 2)
    - 1989-1993 (Box 3)
    - 1994-1996 (Box 4)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 5)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 6)
    - 2000 (Box 9)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 1996-2001
    - 1996-1999; 2001 (Box 7)
- Media Guides, 1989-ongoing, 1 boxes
  - Men (Box 8)
    - 1989; 1992; 1997; 2000; 2003 (Box 8)
    - 2004-2005; 2008 (Box 8)
  - Women
    - 1996-1997; 2000; 2002 (Box 8)
    - 2003-2006 (Box 8)
  - various dates c.2 (Box 8)